clipngocoupons.com 2013-01-17

# Clipngocoupons.com

### Clipngocoupons Privacy Policy

Clipngocoupons is committed to protecting your privacy in a manner that will allow you to use our services with confidence and comfort. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe: 1). what information Clipngocoupons.com collects; 2). how we use it; 3). Your control over the information you give us and; 4). how we protect your information from theft or unauthorized use. This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Use of the services offered at this site constitutes acceptance of the terms of this Policy. If you have a question about the Privacy Policy, please contact our customer service department. 

**The Information We Collect**

Any information that you provide through the Clipngocoupons.com registration process or responses to offers made available to your through our site is complete voluntary. You always have a choice whether or not to disclose information requested in the survey, registration or offer for or to main opted-in as aClipngocoupons.com user. The information we collect includes contact and postal information (such as name, mailing address and telephone number), e-mail address and demographics information (such as age, interests and additional information). In addition, Clipngocoupons.com may present questions regarding your health. Your participation in these questions is complete voluntary. 

We also think that you should be rewarded for the time it takes to fill out our survey. That's why we provide incentives. In part, that's also why we cannot accept information from those under the age of 18 years. Those under 18 cannot participate in sweepstakes and promotions offered by Clipngocoupons.com or the promotion sponsor. In addition, we do not knowingly collect, use or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If, however, we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a while under the age of 13 has been collected, we will delete it from our records. We encourage parents and guardians to participate in and supervise the online activities of their children.

**How We Use It**

Your information will be used to improve and personalize the offers Clipngocoupons.com sends to your and all of members. By providing your e-mail address to Clipngocoupons.com, you are agreeing to receive periodic e-mail messages from Clipngocoupons.com. Clipngocoupons.com may send you e-mail messages regarding marketing offers from other reputable organizations whose products and services we think you might find interesting. Contact, postal, e-mail address and demographic information may we shared with third party marketers for marketing purposes. Similarly, your answers to health related questions may be used or shared to market or advertise products, goods or services to you. By completing health related questions on the survey, you are consenting to the use of this information for direct marketing purposes. In addition, Clipngocoupons.com provides services for direct marketing applications including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation. 

**The Controls You Have On The Information You Share**

If you do not want us to share contact, postal, e-mail address and demographic information with third party marketers, we can add your name to our "do-not-share" or "do-not-call" list. Please click here to send us a request to be added to this list.

Additionally, you may request to unsubscribe from all Clipngocoupons.com related emails by clicking here.   
Unsubscribe requests are processed within 72 hours but because of time lags due to scheduling, you may receive one or two additional e-mail messages that are already "in the pipeline." To remove yourself from third-party mailing lists, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided or contact the third-party directly with your request for removal.

If you supply Clipngocoupons.com with your postal address, you may receive periodic postal mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. You may also receive mailings from other reputable companies. If you do not want to receive postal mail from Clipngocoupons.com or other reputable companies, please contact our customer service group. Please provide us with your exact name and address and we will be sure your name is removed from our postal list.

If you give us your telephone number, you may receive calls from Clipngocoupons.com or other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-call list by clicking here. You can also submit your request online by using this form.

**Security**

Clipngocoupons.com takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Although Clipngocoupons.com does not collect sensitive data like credit card information or Social Security numbers and therefore offers a significantly reduced incentive for data theft, we take very seriously our responsibility to protect your private information. Internally, we restrict access to your information to employees who need access to the information in order for them to do their jobs. These employees are limited in number and are committed to our privacy and security policies. Finally, the servers on which we store your information are kept in a secure environment.

**Additional Information**

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**

Due to popular request, we use persistent, non-identifying cookies if, and only if, you request that we remember your entry or registration information. If we remember your information, you can avoid re-typing that information the next time you enter a survey or drawing. This use of persistent cookies is especially useful for people who enter our drawings daily. You can still use our site even if you have turned off your browser's ability to receive cookies. Cookies also enable us to better match your interests with marketing offers from reputable companies. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site and in HTML e-mail messages (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Clipngocoupons.com does not use pixel tags on our web site. Our e-mail messages contain pixel tags for the purpose of determining if your e-mail software or service can display html-formatted e-mail. This helps us optimize the size of our e-mail messages and conserve bandwidth. Third party pixel tags may be displayed on our site or in our e-mail messages. See "Third Party Ads" below.

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitor traffic, and aggregate demographic data. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Third Party Ads**

Clipngocoupons works with third parties to serve ads and promotions through this site as well as to assist us in managing customer information and to communicate with you. These parties include, but are not limited to Avenue A, Advertising.com and DoubleClick.net. To find out more about how these third parties manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please visit the privacy policy on their web sites.. 

**Third Party Services**

From time-to-time, we may partner with other parties to provide specific services. It may be necessary to share names, or other contact information with a third party(ies) to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Clipngocoupons.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website. When you are on the Clipngocoupons.com site or are accessing a Clipngocoupons.com promotion through an advertising vehicle, and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Clipngocoupons.com. Promotions, surveys and other sweepstakes offerings may be sponsored, or co-sponsored, by another company. Some or all of the data collected during such a program may be shared with the marketing partner. Your participation is always voluntary.

**Sale, Merger or Reorganization**

Clipngocoupons.com may transfer, sell or assign information concerning your use of this Site, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your use of the Site, to third parties, as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, changing control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Clipngocoupons.com.

**Special Disclosure Exceptions**

In some cases, we may disclose your personal information with other third parties if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: Comply with the law; Protect and defend our rights and property; Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site and/or Clipngocoupons.com; or Protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

**Notification of Changes**

Clipngocoupons.com may from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or in part, at its sole discretion. Please check this page periodically for changes. Use of this site shall constitute acceptance of the change and this Policy. 

Last Updated 12:00 PM EST, 5/06/11
